(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T17:24:39.309277",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live
[FBKINGDOM ANTHEM - Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: Information for Visitors]
受注生産グッズ
[Made-to-Order Merchandise]
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live
[FBKINGDOM ANTHEM - Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live]
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
The song I wanted to sing wasn't included.
だったら JOYSOUND X1 で歌おうぜ！
Sing with JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 オンリーワン
JOYSOUND X1, the one and only.
JOYSOUND X1 曲数No.1
JOYSOUND X1, No. 1 in songs.
AIが採点 絶賛サークル
AI scoring and raving circles.
カラオケ最高、最高
Karaoke is the best!
JOYSOUNDなら歌いたい曲があるって最高！
Having the songs you want to sing on JOYSOUND is the best!
JOYSOUND X1
本日は 白上フブキ ファーストソロライブ
Today, thank you for attending Shirakami Fubuki's
「FBKINGDOM ANTHEM」にご来場いただき ありがとうございます
1st Solo Live, "FBKINGDOM ANTHEM"!
ハーイどうもみなさんこんばんきーつねです！
Hi everyone, it's Konbakkitsune!
白上ふぶきでーす！ハーフレンズー！
I'm Fubuki Shirakami! Hi Friends!
わあ、たくさん盛り上がってオルー！いえいえいえい！
Wow, you're getting so hyped up! Yay!
さてさてライブを最後まで楽しんでいっていただけるために、いくつかいい声の白上さんがご案内させていただきますっ。
Now, to make sure you enjoy the live to the very end, I will guide you with a nice voice.
公演中の撮影、録画、録音機器の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and audio devices are strictly prohibited during the show.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside. Please refrain from smoking.
お、いい声だ！
Oh, what a nice voice!
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず近くのスタッフへおしらせください。
If you feel unwell, please don't push yourself and notify nearby staff.
はーい！
Okay!
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど他の皆さんの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Mosh pits, dives, throwing objects on stage, or disturbing others is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have fun.
はーい！
Okay!
はい、いつもの白上さんです。また本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り皆さんが映り込む場合があります。
Yes, it's the usual Shirakami. Also, streaming and photo cameras may capture the audience.
映ってるー！
We're on camera!
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますのであらかじめご容赦ください。
Please note these images may be used for promotions, so please understand.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは#フブキングダムです！ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Also, the live hashtag is #FubukiKingdom! Please use it to hype it up!
おお、いい返事だ！
Oh, great response!
それでは開演までもう少しです。みんな声出す準備できてるよなー！
Well then, curtain-up is just a little longer. Everyone ready to make some noise?!
「Oh my god」
Oh my god
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」っぽいな
Spoilers for love sound like "we're breaking up"
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」っぽいな
Spoilers for life sound like "we're going to die"
なにそれ意味深で かっこいいじゃん…
What's with that deep and cool meaning...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ
Dancing to a collection of buzzwords
失敬
Excuse me
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu "style"
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
It's so typical, so typical
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu "style"
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu
神っぽいな
It's god-like
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
Enough already, enough of that
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたなあ
I'm getting even more excited
おっきいね おっきいね 夢
So big, so big, a dream
おっきいね おっきいね
So big, so big
景気いいけど 品性はTHE END
Things are booming, but decency is the end
うええい うええい
Yay, yay
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
It's god-like, that's unfair
神っぽいな それ "My God"
It's god-like, that's "My God"
アイウォンチュー ウォンチュー
I want you, want you
IQが下がっていく感じ
Feeling my IQ dropping
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
It's evil-minded, after all
邪心っぽいな それ "My God"
It's evil-minded, that's "My God"
アイヘイチュー ヘイチュー
I hate you, hate you
害虫はどっち
Which one is the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that makeup
アレっぽいな それ 比況
It's like that, that's peer comparison
アレっぽいな それ
It's like that, that's
その名言 その意見 その批評
Those famous quotes, opinions, criticisms
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, gag, and sense
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
It's god-like, that's unfair
っぽいな っぽいな っぽい 憧れちゃう！
It's so god-like, I admire it!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu "style"
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
It's so typical, so typical
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu "style"
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu
神っぽいな
It's god-like
メタ思考する本質は悪意?
Is the essence of meta-thinking malice?
人を小馬鹿にしたような作為
Artifice that mocks people
無為に生き延びるのは難しい
It's hard to survive idly
権力に飲まれて揺らぐ灯り
A flickering light swallowed by power
神を否定し神に成り代わり
Denying god and taking god's place
玉座で豹変する小物達
Small fry changing tune on the throne
批判に見せかけ自戒の祈り
Prayers of self-reproach disguised as critique
"Dou you know?"
何言ってんの? それ ウザい 何言ってんの? それ
What are you saying? That's annoying.
意味がよくわかんないし
I don't really get the meaning
眠っちゃうよ まじ
I'm seriously gonna fall asleep
飽きっぽいんだ オーケー みんな飽きっぽいんだ オーケー
Everyone gets bored easily, okay
踊れるやつちょうだいちょうだい beam...
Give me something danceable, beam...
kiss hoi ne kiss hoi ne
それ kiss hoi ne kiss hoi ne 逆にファンになってきたじゃん
I'm actually starting to become a fan
ちっちかいね ちっちかいね
So small, so small
器ちっちかいね ちっちかいね
Such a small vessel, so small
天才ゆえ孤独ですね
Solitary because of genius
"Kak kee... kak kee!!"
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
It's god-like, that's unfair
神っぽいな それ "My God"
It's god-like, that's "My God"
超健康 健康 言い張って
Insisting on being super healthy
くたばっていく感じ
Feeling like dropping dead
ヤケっぽいな それ 畢竟
It's desperate, after all
ヤケっぽいな それ "My God"
It's desperate, that's "My God"
もう哀愁 哀愁 エピゴーンヌのヒール
Already sorrow, sorrow, the heel of the epigone
ゲマの皆さん 準備はできてますか？
Gamers, are you ready?
セイホーフォーレ 行きますよ！
Safe and Follow! Let's go!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はい！はい！うーこっこーん！
Hai! Hai! U-kokon!
ふー！
Woo!
せーの！ Are you READY?
Ready? Are you ready?
会いたかったって会っちゃってさ
We wanted to meet, and now we finally have,
いつもの場所から 元気にせーのでご挨拶！
greeting you cheerfully from our usual place!
初めましてはおしゃべりをして
We chat when we first meet,
けむとすらすら そんな毎日が愛おしくて
and such smooth, everyday moments are so precious.
あれもこれも手を出し たくなりガチです
We tend to reach out for this and that,
ステップはまだまだ恥ずかしいけど 支え合ってほら届けてますよ この声は
and though our steps are still clumsy, supporting each other, we deliver this voice to you!
セイ！ほらその顔上げて みんなで手を取れば
Say! Come on, lift your faces, if we all hold hands,
さあまだまだ見たことない世界を越えよ
come on, let's transcend a world we've never seen yet!
セイ！ほら推し推し様も 止まない戦力ですから
Say! Come on, even our beloved oshi are an unstoppable force,
夢を書き換えたら 追いかけ続けよ 共に繋がるファンファーレ ゴー！
so once you rewrite your dreams, keep chasing them! A fanfare connecting us together, go!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はい！はい！うーこっこーん！
Hai! Hai! U-kokon!
ふー！
Woo!
せーの！ Go! Go! Let's GO!
Ready? Go! Go! Let's GO!
ちょっとやらかした時でも 気持ち切り替えて
Even when we make a slight mistake, we switch our mood
ぼーっとしちゃう昼下がりは 背伸びをして
and stretch during lazy afternoons.
お腹減ったら すぐもぐもぐと お茶の時間は
When we get hungry, we munch right away, tea time is
こんなやつで 黒いあの子にはナイショにしてほしいです
like this, I want you to keep it a secret from that black one.
仲間の力とお友達の皆さんと 叶えたい夢は言葉にして 一つ一つ
Turning the power of our friends and everyone into words, one by one,
セイ！ほらその手を上げて みんなでファンになれば
Say! Come on, raise your hands, if we all become fans,
さあまだまだ成長中 問題ないでしょ
come on, we're still growing, so there's no problem!
セイ！ほら明るく元気な 心がとりえですから
Say! Come on, because a bright and cheerful heart is our best trait,
へこみちな時も 気持ち切り替えて
even during gloomy times, we switch our mood...
輝き続けよう 共に繋ぐアンコール
Let's keep shining, connecting our encore together!
Say! Go! Yay!
歌えみんな 声 全然足りないぞ
Sing, everyone! Your voices are nowhere near enough!
まだまだ声 出せるよなー！
You can still raise your voices more, right?!
うー！GO! GO! LET'S GO!
Woo! Go! Go! Let's go!
何もかもが新しくて 右も左も分からない時も
Even when everything is brand new and I don't know left from right,
頑張れたのは みんながいたから
I was able to do my best because everyone was here.
一つ一つ応援が 愛おしくなって 一歩ずつでも
Every single cheer became so dear, step by step,
私が自分で紡いでいくフューチャー
The future I'm weaving by myself.
答えも夢もまだまだ手探りしても
Even if answers and dreams are still fumbled in the dark,
響き合ってほら 世界は今 一際目いて
resonating together, look, the world is now standing out brilliantly—
さあ その顔上げて みんなで手を取れば
Come on, raise your heads, if we hold hands together,
最高潮の夢の先へ駆け出そう
let's dash towards the peak of our dreams!
ほら おしおごとも 止まらない戦力ですから
Look, even chatting nonstop is our unstoppable power,
大好きな甘いが溢れそうなほど 共に繋ぐファンファーレ！GO! YEAH!
so much that our favorite sweetness overflows, connecting together in a fanfare! Go! Yeah!
はい！はい！うー！ぽこん！ぽーん！
Hai! Hai! Woo! Pokon! Pon!
ぽこん！ぽーん！はい！ライブ わくわく わくわく
Pokon! Pon! Hai! Live, excited, excited!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい！はい！うー！ぽこん！ぽーん！はい！はい！はい！はい！ワン ツー スリー フォックス！
Hai! Hai! Woo! Pokon! Pon! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! One, Two, Three, Fox!
イェーイ！
Yay!
皆さん 本日はフブキングダムへようこそ！
Everyone, welcome to Fubukingdom today!
みんなの声、そして私の歌をこの横浜に響かせるぞー！
Let's make everyone's voices and my songs echo through Yokohama!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい！はい！フォックス！
Hai! Hai! Fox!
ごきげんね 私は白上フブキです
How are you? I'm Shirakami Fubuki,
お姉ちゃんとゲームが大好きで おんなのばーちゃるきつねです
an older sister-like virtual fox who loves games.
いろんなことで毎日楽しく活動をしているので フブちゃん、フブさん、白上皆さん お好きに呼んでください！
Since I have fun doing activities every day with all sorts of things, please call me however you like!
動画初めてのずっとも もっとぐせってずっとも
Friends since my very first video, friends who keep on getting closer,
一人一人の足からぜ 私が真ん中にいます！はい！
from everyone's steps, I am right in the middle! Hai!
はい！はい！うー！ぽこん！ぽーん！はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Woo! Pokon! Pon! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
どこまでもずーっと来れないかな場所で
In a place where we can go on forever,
君もいつだって押したってウェルカムフェン まだまだみんなの中
you are always welcome here, still in everyone's hearts,
あわただしく過ぎる日々は 宝物なんですよ
days that rush by busily are such treasures.
泣いたって怒ったって大ジョブじゃい 笑顔で一緒にはい！はい！フォックス！
It's okay even if you cry or get mad, together with a smile, hai! hai! fox!
こころを下に重ねて 届けましょうマイハッピーデイ！
Layering our hearts below, let's deliver my happy day!
始まろう 今日は何をして遊びましょうか
Let's begin, what shall we play today?
お茶でも飲んで一息ついて 今日はソロライブ！
Have some tea, take a breath, today is a solo live!
皆さんのこともう少し知れたら私も幸せなので ぴったりがったりアピールしたりみんなせのでご一緒に！
If I get to know you a bit more, I'll be happy too, so let's stick together, appeal, and all together!
打ち解けて飛び跳ねる時ま 打ち解けて打ち込める時ま
When we open up and jump around, when we open up and get immersed,
あなたのそばでちょこん！私頑張りかにいます！
right by your side, chokon! I'll do my best!
はい！はい！うー！ぽこん！ぽーん！はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Woo! Pokon! Pon! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
どこまでもずーっと来れない甘いだから
Because it's so sweet we can go on anywhere,
君と誰だって押したってウェルカムフェン まんちーまーつフェイチャー中
you and anyone, push and welcome, in the middle of a munchi-matsu feature.
同じ時はすぐ今が幸せなんですよ 泣いたって怒ったって大ジョブじゃい 笑顔で一緒にはい！はい！フォックス！
The same time is happiness right now, it's okay even if you cry or get mad, together with a smile, hai! hai! fox!
輝く色を重ねて 広げましょうマイブランドニューワールド！
Layering shining colors, let's spread my brand new world!
いつでも回ってはたった 一度きりの人生を
Spinning around anytime, a once-in-a-lifetime life,
詰まって詰まって詰まって 心はたよわせよう
jammed and jammed, let's align our hearts.
どこまで届けるよ ただし知ってるよ だんだんね繋がるよ ここから始めよう
How far will it reach? But I know, little by little we connect, let's start from here.
あー！さあさあみんなの声を聞かせてくれ！
Ah! Come on, let me hear everyone's voices!
もっともっと大きく聞かせてよね！ 行きますよ！ 声を合わせて一緒にせーの！
Let me hear it louder and bigger! Here we go! Voices together, ready, set, go!
シロッコ みんな歌え! みんなさんに届け!
Shirokko, everyone sing! Reach everyone!
せーのっ! 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 1, 2, 3, 4
Ready, go! 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 1, 2, 3, 4
おじいちゃんもおばあちゃんもお兄ちゃんも姉ちゃんも!
Grandpa, grandma, big brother, and big sister too!
ここまでよくできました!
You've done well to make it this far!
最後にひとつ!
Just one more thing at the end!
3000回でも足りないぞ 100万回愛してる!
3,000 times isn't enough, I love you a million times!
これまでを支えてくれてさ
Thank you for supporting me up until now,
みんなに寄り添いたいなって
I want to stay close to everyone.
大切なんだからずっと、これからも、今も、ずっと、大好きなこの場所で
Because it's precious, always, from now on, even now, in this place I love so much,
君もいったって押したってウェルカム! ワクワク更新中
Welcome whether you go or push! Excitement is updating.
求め明日も未来も、お友達だよ!
Seeking tomorrow and the future too, we're friends!
泣いたって怒ったって大好きじゃん!
Whether crying or angry, I still love you!
笑顔で一緒にハイハイハイ!
High five together with a smile!
心を二人に重ねて、届けましょう!
Layer our hearts in two and let it reach!
つなげましょう、そう、シャイニースマイル!
Let's connect, yes, a shiny smile!
さあ横浜! もっともっと盛り上がっていこうか!
Now Yokohama! Let's get even more hyped up!
みんな手振って声出して、いけますよね? 全曲でいけますよね?
Everyone wave your hands and raise your voices, you can do it, right? For all songs, right?
声が小さい! いけますよね? 声が小さい! いけますよね?
Your voice is too small! You can do it, right? Your voice is too small! You can do it, right?
ありがとう! 最後まで楽しんでいってください!
Thank you! Please enjoy it until the very end!
新たなように、いくぞ!
Like anew, let's go!
切り開いてる、私の世界
Paving the way, my world,
どこまで行く、あの銀河の中で
how far will it go, within that galaxy.
探し出す足、言葉並べてしまった彩りなのか
Searching feet, is it a colorful display of lined-up words?
少し笑った、君とともに歩んできた
I smiled a little, walking alongside you.
夜の果てを思い出し歌う
Singing, remembering the end of the night,
言葉にならない感情ことすべて、今届けたい
I want to deliver all these emotions that can't be put into words, right now.
君が愛してくれるから、君を愛してるから、切なさの今が輝いてく
Because you love me, because I love you, the present of heartache shines bright.
千の星空を見上げちょうだい、このスピードで最高のように
Look up at a thousand starry skies, at this speed, like the best.
いつでも愛に行こう
Let's always go meet.
信じてる、私の未来
I believe in my future,
積み重ねる良い欲望かな
piling up good desires.
そして昨日の現実感が曖昧になっていくそんな毎日でも
Even in such days where yesterday's reality becomes vague,
だとしてもとっても大事なことは、自分のことも愛せることだ
even so, the most important thing is being able to love yourself.
多少うまくできないときだってまたやり直そう
Even when you can't do things very well, let's try again.
君が愛せなくなっても君を愛してるから切なさの光が輝いてく
Even if you can't love, I love you, so the light of heartache shines bright.
千の星空を見上げちょうだい、このスピードで心繋ぐ
Look up at a thousand starry skies, connecting hearts at this speed.
もっともっと声出して!
Raise your voices even more!
まだ足りないぞ!
Still not enough!
愛!愛!愛!愛!
Love! Love! Love! Love!
もっともっと声出して!
Raise your voices even more!
千の言葉じゃ何をも伝わらない
A thousand words cannot convey anything,
一日強く噛みしめなら
if you bite down strongly on each day.
この新時代の
This new era's
いの一番のドグラマッタだけ
The absolute top priority...
君だけが愛してくれるから
Because only you will love me,
君を愛してるから 切なさの今が諦めてく
Because I love you, this anguish is fading away.
線の星屑を網羅み上げてさ
Gathering up the stardust on the lines,
新生のスピードで最後のよに
at breakneck speed, like it's the very end—
今愛にいく
Now, I'm going to meet you!
ピアリーナにキングが帰ってきたぞ！
The king has returned to the Piarena!
国民のみんな まだ声出したりないよね！？
Citizens! You haven't cheered enough yet, right?!
いけるよね！？
You can go harder, right?!
アリーナ！
Arena!
散々！散々！散々！散々！
Brilliant! Brilliant! Brilliant! Brilliant!
そして今このライブも見てくれてるみんな！
And to everyone watching this live right now!
アリーナ！
Arena!
せーの！
Ready, set!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなー！
Everyone!
はぁ、やばい もうやばいんですけども皆さん！聞こえてますって！コンコンキツネー！
Man, this is crazy. I can hear you! Kon-kon kitsune!
ほらライブ一斉制限！ゲームオーズキング！みんなの王様白上フブキでーす！
Hololive 1st Generation! Everyone's king, Shirakami Fubuki here!
いやー街に待ったこの日が遂にやってきましたよー！
Man, this day we've been waiting for has finally arrived!
すごかった！みんな3曲連続だけどよくついてこれましたね！すごかった！
It was amazing! You kept up with three songs in a row! Amazing!
さすがです！
Truly impressive!
いやー白と黄色のみんなの声聞きながらもう煽っていくしかねぇと！負けじ負けじとねみんなの声出してけって感じで
Hearing your voices, I had to hype you up even more!
ねえ、もう素晴らしかったです！ありがとうございます！
Hey, it was just wonderful! Thank you so much!
ちょっとね、お水も飲みたいんですけども、えー今日ですね、まああのフブキングダム、建国祝祭みたいな感じなんですけども、みんなね今日フブキングダムの歌にゅうこくってちょっと持ってませんか？
Today is like the Fubuki Kingdom's founding anniversary, so... did you all bring your entry permits?
持ってってる？もしかして？ いやちがうよみんな！
You brought them? No, wait, everyone!
ここはもうフブキングダムからみんなの実家だから、おかえりー！
This place is everyone's hometown since it's Fubuki Kingdom, so welcome back!
そう、そうでみんなは帰ってきたんだこの国にね！
That's right, everyone came back to this country!
ちょっともう一回やろうかなみんな！おかえりー！
Let's do that one more time, everyone! Welcome back!
おおー！ありがとー！
Ooh! Thank you!
もっとねこの後もいっぱいいっぱい歌う予定なので、もっとね声たくさん聞かせてくださいねー！
There's going to be a lot more singing, so let me hear your voices!
そしてですね本日は素敵な演奏でライブを盛り上げてくれるですね、バンドメンバーの方々がいらっしゃいますー！
And today, we have the wonderful band members hyping up the live!
かっこいい！もうね最高の楽曲をですね、このピアリーナエムエム全身で味わってください！
So cool! Enjoy the best music with your entire body at Piarena MM!
はい！今回のライブなんですけども、なんと海外でもねライブビューイングさせていただいておりますー！
For this live, we're also holding live viewings overseas!
ハイフレンズ！見ってるー？配信のディー席の皆さーん！
Hi friends! Are you watching? Everyone in the streaming seats!
ライブビューイングの皆さんですね、エンジョイフブキングダムもあんせむもいっぱいね最後まで見てってくださいー！
Live viewing audience, enjoy Fubuki Kingdom to the end!
ふう、そして、おー！D席の皆さんもよう見えとるぞ！みんなもアピールしてほら！
Whew, I can see the D-seat audience clearly too! Show your appeal, look!
会場の皆もD席の皆にイエーイって！イエーイ！
Everyone at the venue, say "Yay!" to the D-seat folks! Yay!
コメントとかもね、しっかり見てますので、ちゃんと皆さんコメントもいっぱいいっぱいしてくださいね！お伺いしまーす！
I'm reading the comments too, so please leave lots of comments! Please!
ですね ちょっと残念なお知らせがあるんですけども
Well, I have some unfortunate news, but...
知ってもいいかな？ちょっとお知らせします！
Do you want to hear it? Let me announce it!
えーー
Uhh—
なんと
Believe it or not,
無料パートをやっているんですけども
we're currently doing a free part,
今YouTubeとTikTokで
right now on YouTube and TikTok,
なんとそれを見ているスポンポアはですね
and surprisingly, the sponsors watching this...
ここまでとなります！
will end right here!
ここまでだ！
That's as far as it goes!
はい！
Yep!
もっともっと盛り上がりたいよっていうね、国民の皆は！
For all you citizens who want to get even more hyped,
チケットを買って！
please buy a ticket!
最後まで一緒に楽しんでください！
And enjoy it together with us until the very end!
お願いします！
Please!
さてさて
Now then,
じゃあ皆さん、まだまだね、いっぱい歌聞きたいですよね？
everyone, you still want to hear lots more songs, right?
まだまだ盛り上がっていけるよな！
We can get even more hyped up, right?!
お、なんかちょっとさっき歌ってる時に聞いた声よりちっちゃいぞ！
Oh, that sounded a bit quieter than the voices I heard while singing earlier!
盛り上がっていけるよな！
We can get even more hyped, right?!
最高！
Awesome!
よし、フブキングダムワンセブン、楽しんでいきましょう！
Alright, let's enjoy FBKINGDOM 1st LIVE together!